# **ALEBIOSU VICTORIA IKOTUN**

@ alebiosu89@gmail.com

**\** 07065652382

Block18 plot 450, AbdulFatai Mogaji street, Genesis Estate, Akinola Aboru Iyana Ipaja Lagos.

5th September 2019

#### Miss Victoria Odimba

Head Hi-Impact T.V Hi-Impact Television Km12, Lagos -Ibadan Expressway, Opp, MFM prayer city, Ibafo.

**Re:** Application for a presenter.

Miss Victoria Odimba

I wish to apply for the role of a presenter, recently advertised on a group chat'. Please find enclosed my CV for your consideration.

As you can see from my attached CV, I have over three years' experience in the media. I'm ready for a new challenge in your medium, and see this position as the perfect role to help me achieve this.

I'm particularly interested in working as a presenter because of my passion for reading news and anchoring programs, something I've had extensive experience of during my time in presenting. Further, I feel that I have achieved all that I can in my current industry.

Throughout my previous positions I have content ranging called her voice. This is when female voice are been heard, it a talk and phone in program, which cut across female child abuse, marriage challenges, relationship issues and lot more.

In my previous role as a Teleprompter and correspondence, I was responsible for managing the teleprompter and teleprompting news for the news casters and also reading of voice over. I went further for upgrading at National broadcast Academy (The Training Arm of Federal Radio cooperation of Nigeria) to enhance my skills in presenting.

Thank you for your time and consideration. I look forward to meeting with you to discuss my application further.

Yours sincerely,

Alebiosu Victoria Ikotun

### CONTACT

### **ALEBIOSU VICTORIA IKOTUN**

@ alebiosu89@gmail.com

**\** 07065652382

Block18 plot 450, AbdulFatai Mogaji street, Genesis Estate, Akinola Aboru Iyana Ipaja Lagos.

# **OBJECTIVE**

To enhance my professional skills, capabilities and knowledge in an organization which recognizes the value of hard work and trusts me with responsibilities and challenges.

### **EXPERIENCE**

2017 - 2019

# o Core TV News, Discovery garden Isheri Ogunstate

News Teleprompter \ correspondent

- Teleprompt news with the help of teleprompter for the newscasters to view
- Correespond news stories and read voice over.

#### 2016 - 2017

### Guaranteed Trust Bank (GTB)

Customer service representative

- Be the eyes and voice of the company
- Attained to customers complain
- o Profer solutions to their complains.

#### 2013 - 2014

# Modern Acme College

Supervisor

Supervise the activities of the staffs

# **EDUCATION**

2019

 National Broadcasting Academy, 1A Adekunle Fajuyi way, GRA Ikeja, La Certificate in Broadcasting.

2016

Ngerian Institute of journalism Ogba ljaiye

Higher National Diploma

Upper credit

2010

o Dataxross computer school, Sango Ota, Ogunstate

Certificate in desktop publishing

Upper credit

2007

Ansar un Deen comprehensive college. Ota, Ogun state

High school

### **SKILLS**

- Sales
- Team building
- Problem solving
- Decision making

# REFERENCE

Mrs. Patricia Kalesanwo - "Nigerian institute of journalism"
Student affairs
07039221173

Deacon S.Olaniyi Toye - "Berger Paints"
Civil servant
08084250898